ADETOBA ADEDEJI

Lagos, Nigeria



adedeji006@gmail.com



+2347063935898



linkedin.com/in/adetoba-adedeji



https://adetoba-adedeji.netlify.app/

Summary

I am a creative and result-oriented developer with experience in web applications. My primary focus is on the frontend in other to build Apps that create greats experience for users. Responsive web design in software development is my favorite and as a result, I create responsive and interactive websites. My design approach follows the mobile-first principle so as to give access and create better experiences for all users irrespective of their devices.

I have two years of learning and working experience in this field and I work with the following languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6+, and TypeScript.

I'm experienced using the following frameworks/libraries: Material-UI, Sass (SCSS), Styled-Components, Tailwind, React, Redux (Redux ToolKit), and Next.

I also make use of platforms/tools such as VS-Code, Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Jira, and Slack.

Experience



Frontend Developer

Digiscript | Tech Solutions

Oct 2021 - Present (4 months +)

- Implementing frontend features of multiple web projects
- · Collaborating with other developers and designers to execute client's projects
- Report daily to the CTO on the progress of each project

Frontend Developer (Intern)

HNG Internship

Aug 2021 - Oct 2021 (3 months)

- Worked in a team where I was a sub-team lead for the frontend team in charge of implementing the UI
- Responsible for assigning tasks to other frontend developers in my team
- Provided detailed feedbacks to other developers on each task given to them
- Communicated with other sub-teams within the project group
- I was one of the maintainers of the project's codebase and GitHub activities for the group

Education



🚮 Obafemi Awolowo University

Bachelor's degree, Chemical Engineering 2015 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications

Jobberman Soft Skills Course - Coursera E6HSAC4JQG52

Front-End Web Development with React - Coursera
TVXTBHS3LN7Y

Advanced Styling with Responsive Design - Coursera 87ZSRUR75YJ3

Skills

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • TypeScript • Tailwind CSS • styled-components • React.js • Redux.js • Next.js • Git